<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Jokes>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a dog who does magic tricks? A labracadabrador!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What did the duck say when he bought lipstick? Put it on my bill!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why couldn't the leopard play hide and seek? Because he was always spotted!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a pig that does Karate? A pork chop</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What's the difference between a guitar and a fish? You can tune a guitar, but you can't tuna fish</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the fish blush? Because it saw the ocean's bottom</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do the french eat snails? They don't like fast food!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What type of sandals do frogs wear? Open toad!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get from a pampered cow? Spoiled milk</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get when you cross a snake and a bakery? A python!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What is out of bounds? An exhausted kangaroo</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a bear with no ears? A b!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a sleeping bull? A bull-dozer.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>How do you fit more pigs on your farm? Build a sty-scraper!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What did the farmer call the cow that had no milk? An udder failure.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do gorillas have big nostrils? Because they have big fingers!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get from a pampered cow? Spoiled milk.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why are teddy bears never hungry? They are always stuffed!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do fish live in salt water? Because pepper makes them sneeze!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get from a pampered cow? Spoiled milk.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Where do polar bears vote? The North Poll</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What did the judge say when the skunk walked in the court room? Odor in the court!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What sound do porcupines make when they kiss? Ouch!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the snake cross the road? To get to the other ssssssside!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why are fish so smart? Because they live in schools.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a cow that won't give milk? A milk dud!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>When is a well dressed lion like a weed? When he's a dandelion</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>How does a lion greet the other animals in the field? Pleased to eat you.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What happened when the lion ate the comedian? He felt funny!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What fish only swims at night? A starfish!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why is a fish easy to weigh? Because it has its own scales!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get when a chicken lays an egg on top of a barn? An eggroll!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why didn't the chicken cross the road? Because there was a KFC on the other side!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the chicken cross the road? To show everyone he wasn't chicken!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the lion spit out the clown? Because he tasted funny!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the turkey cross the road? To prove he wasn't chicken!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What animals are on legal documents? Seals!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get when you cross a snake and a pie? A pie-thon!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What is 'out of bounds'? An exhausted kangaroo!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What did the buffalo say to his son when he went away on a trip? Bison!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why didn't the boy believe the tiger? He thought it was a lion!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>How do bees get to school? By school buzz!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a bear with no ears? B!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What animal has more lives than a cat? Frogs, they croak every night!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What's the most musical part of a chicken? The drumstick</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What's a frog's favorite soda? Croak-a-Cola</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the elephants get kicked out of the public pool? They kept dropping their trunks.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get when you put three ducks in a box? A box of quackers</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call an alligator who is a thief? A crookodile</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call an illegally parked frog? Toad.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do cats have for breakfast? Mice Crispies</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a fish without an eye? Fsh</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText> Where did the sheep go on vacation? The baaaahamas</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What kind of cars do cats drive? Catillacs!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText> What happened when the lion ate the comedian? He felt funny!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What’s a funny fish called? A clownfish</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What kind of ties do pigs wear? Pig sties</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you say if you meet a toad? Wart’s new?</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a gorilla wearing earmuffs? Anything you like, he can’t hear you</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why are teddy bears never hungry? They are always stuffed!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What to polar bears eat for lunch? Ice berg-ers</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What is a dog's favorite city? New Yorkie</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a dog magician? A Labracadabrador</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Which animal always cheats on tests? A cheetah</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What did the buffalo say to his son when he left for college? Bison</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What is a cat's favourite color? Purr-ple</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What are caterpillars afraid of? Dogger-pillars</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What animals are the best pets? Cats, because they are purr-fect</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the leopard wear a striped shirt? So he wouldn't be spotted</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What is a cat's favorite song? Three Blind Mice</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do bees have sticky hair? Because they have honeycombs</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get when you cross a sheepdog with a rose? A collie-flower!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What happened to the dog that ate nothing but garlic? His bark was much worse than his bite!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What’s the difference between a cat and a frog? Well, a cat has nine lives, but a frog croaks every night!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do fish swim in salt water? Because pepper makes them sneeze  </JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do birds fly south in the winter? Because it’s too far to walk</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a chicken at the North Pole? Lost</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a girl cow in Spanish? Moo-chacha</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do ducks watch on TV? Duck-umentaries</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a grizzly bear caught in the rain? A drizzly bear</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What kind of cats like to go bowling? Alley cats</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What is black and white and red all over? A panda bear with a sunburn</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do bears have fur coats? Because they look silly wearing jackets</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get when you cross a chicken with a cow? Roost beef</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get when you cross a cocker spaniel, a poodle and a rooster? Cockerpoodledoo</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the bee go to the doctor? Because he had hives</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What steps do you take if you a tiger is running towards you? Big ones</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What does a mixed-up hen lay? Scrambled eggs</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do gorillas have big nostrils? Because they have big fingers</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a parrot when it has dried itself after a bath? Polly unsaturated!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do bees do if they want to use public transport? Wait at a buzz stop!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why does a rooster watch TV? For Hen-tertainment!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Which kinds of snakes are found on cars? Windshield vipers.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What did one flea say to the other flea when they came out of the movies? Should we walk home or take a dog?</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>How do most frogs die? They kermit suicide!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>How do bees get to school? They ride the school buzz</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What sound do porcupines make when they kiss? Ouch!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>How does a squid go into battle? Well Armed</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call an arctic cow? An eski-moo!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the dolphin cross the beach? To get to the other tide</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What is the easiest way to count a herd of cows? Use a cow-culator</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why are giraffes so slow to apologize? It takes them a long time to swallow their pride.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why are elephants never rich? Because they work for peanuts!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Did you hear the story about the skunk? Never mind, it stinks!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the lamb run over the cliff? He didn’t see the ewe turn!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the foal go to the doctor? Because he was a little horse</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the rooster cross the road? To cock-a-doodle-doo something</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the turkey cross the road? To prove she wasn’t chicken</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why did the chicken cross the road, roll in the mud, and cross the road again? Because she was a dirty double-crosser</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What bird can be heard at mealtimes? A swallow</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do cows like being told jokes? Because they like being a-moosed!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What kind of ant is even bigger than an elephant? A gi-ant</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What’s in the middle of a jellyfish? It’s jelly-button</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you call a baby monkey? A chimp off the old block.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What did the duck say to the bartender? Put it on my bill</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Where does fish keep their money? In a river-bank!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>When is it bad luck to see a black cat? When you’re a mouse!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why is it easy to spot Cinderella-fish? They have glass flippers!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What steps will you take if a tiger is running towards you? Big steps.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>How do prawns and clams communicate? With shell-phones!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why would an octopus versus squid war be terrible? They are both well-armed!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What fur do we get from a Tiger? As fur away as possible!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why does the ocean twinkle at night? It’s full of starfish!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do you get when you cross an octopus and a cow? An animal that can milk itself!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why oysters do not share their pearls? Because they are shellfish!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>How do fish without cars get around? Octo-bus!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>What do bees do if they want to use public transport? Wait at the buzz stop.</JokeText>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <JokeText>Why do Teddy bears never feel hungry? Because they are always stuffed!</JokeText>
  </Joke>
</Jokes>
